A Guide to the English-Speaking Union, Charlottesville Branch, Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #10599-e
English-Speaking Union Papers 1967-1994
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
10599-e
ca. 200 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was loaned to the University of Virginia Library by the English-Speaking Union, Charlottesville Branch, through Mrs. Katherine Sargeant, Charlottesville, Virginia.
Scope and Content
This addition to the papers of the Charlottesville Branch of the English-Speaking Union consists of ca. 200 items (1.5 Hollinger boxes), 1967, 1988-1994, including minutes of meetings, correspondence, invitations to events, membership records, financial records, program information, speakers information, and various records of the organization kept in a three-ring notebook with notebook dividers.
Contents List
- Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box Box 1)
- Dinners, 1992-1994 (Box Box 1)
- Excellence in English Program, 1992-1993 (Box Box 1)
- Financial Report, 1967, 1992-1993 (Box Box 1)
- Membership, 1992-1994 (Box Box 1)
- Minutes of Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box Box 1)
- National Office, 1992-1994 (Box Box 1)
- Notebook of English-Speaking Union Records, ca. 1988-1990; (4 folders) (Box Box 2)
- Scholarship Program, 1992-1993 (Box Box 2)
- Shakespeare Competition, 1992-1993 (Box Box 2)
- Speakers, 1992-1994 (Box Box 2)